William Kelly Simpson Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
William Kelly Simpson Archives
1958-1998
ANTAR.000011
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
15
; 1 map case
The archives of William Simpson, accumulated during his time at Yale.
Simpson, William Kelly, 1928-
Biographical Sketch
Simpson, William Kelly (b.1928) was appointed to the Yale faculty in 1958. His interests embrace nearly every aspect of Egyptology, including history, literature, art, and archaeology. His numerous books include publications of the Pennsylvania-Yale Expedition to Egypt, Giza mastabas, several volumes of papyri and other Egyptian writings, a standard history of Egypt, and an anthology of Egyptian literature in translation. He is author of nearly 150 articles in the field of Egyptology and serves as editor of the Yale Egyptological Studies. He also served as one of several co-directors of the University of Pennsylvania Museum-Yale University Expedition to Abydos, Egypt.
Education
- B.A. Yale University, 1947
- M.A. Yale University, 1948
- Ph.D. Yale University, 1954
Description of the Material
The archives of William Simpson, accumulated during his time at Yale relating to objects curated at the Peabody Museum.
Egypt; Field notebooks; Photographs; Maps; Correspondence; Yale Peabody Museum; Yale University
- Photographs, Series I
  Scope and Contents
  Including film negatives and slides.
  - Aminna and Toshka. 35mm Negatives from Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 039720
  - Arminna East. Oversized Field Photos from Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 037186
  - Arminna East. Field Photos from Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 038194
  - Arminna West. Field Photos from Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 035192
  - Arminna West. Oversized Field Photos from Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 037187
  - Miscellaneous. Field Photos from Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 035194
  - Miscellaneous. Oversized Field Photos from Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 037958
  - Miscellaneous. Slides from Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 040130
  - Teaching Collection Slides. Medium format glass-mounted black-and-white slides (glass10 cm H x 8.2 cm W; various image sizes). Count of 35 slides from the William Kelly Simpson teaching collection: 9 ofTell Basta; 5 of Sakkara; 2 of Giza; 5 of Dashur; 4 unlabeled texts; 3 unlabeled rock engravings; 6 unlabeled images of statuary; 1 rock engraving labeled "Edward Van Altena"., 040703
  - Teaching Collection Slides. 35mm slides from the William Kelly Simpson teaching collection. Count of 49 black and white / color slides. Miscellaneous Pre-Dynastic, Early Dynastic and Old Kingdom slides. Various images of sculpture, architecture, maps, paintings, and rock engravings., 041081
  - Teaching Collection Slides. 35mm slides from the William Kelly Simpson teaching collection. Count of 75 various black and white / color slides; Middle Kingdom. Images of sculpture, maps, texts, and rock engravings. 1 from Dynasty 11; 63 from Dynasty 12; 11 slides various Middle Kingdom., 041082
  - Teaching Collection Slides. 35mm slides from the William Kelly Simpson teaching collection. Count of 77 various black and white / color slides. Middle Kingdom and Second Intermediate Period. Images of sculpture, architecture and rock inscriptions. 42 slides from Dynasty 12; 1 from dynasty 12-13; 3 from Dynasty 13; 4 from Byblos; 9 miscellaneous;19 from the Second Intermediate Period., 041083
  - Teaching Collection Slides. 35mm slides from the William Kelly Simpson teaching collection. Count of 109 various black and white / color slides; images of sculpture, wall paintings, architecture and rock engravings. New Kingdom, 18th Dynasty, mainly tombs of Paatenemheb, Paheri, Horemheb; also 50 from Luxor; 10 of the Tjawy Relief., 041084
  - Teaching Collection Slides. 35mm slides from the William Kelly Simpson teaching collection. Count of 69 various black and white / color slides; various images of sculpture, ceramics, landscapes, and architecture. New Kingdom, mostly from Amarna, Dynasty 18; also 20 miscellaneous New Kingdom slides., 041085
  - Teaching Collection Slides. 35mm slides from the William Kelly Simpson teaching collection. Count of 101 black and white / color slides. New Kingdom Amarna, 18th dynasty; various images of sculpture, reliefs, engravings, architecture, and maps., 041086
  - Teaching Collection Slides. 35mm slides from the William Kelly Simpson teaching collection. Count of 72 various black and white / color slides; various images of sculpture, architecture, and rock inscriptions. New Kingdom, 18th dynasty. 29 from Deir el Bahri; 11 of Hatshepsut (Deir el Bahri); 17 of Senmut; 3 of the Hyksos Dagger; 12 miscellaneous., 041087
  - Teaching Collection Slides. 35mm slides from the William Kelly Simpson teaching collection. Count of 107 black and white / color slides; all 18th Dynasty reliefs, sculpture, artifacts, and statuary., 041088
  - Teaching Collection Slides. 35mm slides from the William Kelly Simpson teaching collection. Count of 105 black and white / color slides. New Kingdom, 18th Dynasty sculpture and statuary; 19th Dynasty reliefs and sculpture; 19th-20th Dynasty writing, maps, and hieroglyphs; miscellaneous New Kingdom objects and artifacts., 041089
  - Teaching Collection Slides. 35mm slides from the William Kelly Simpson teaching collection. Count of 48 various black and white / color slides; various images of architecture, drawings, sculpture, and rock engravings. New Kingdom, Medinet Habu (18th to 20th Dynasties). Glass slides bound with red tape are fragile, handle with care., 041090
  - Teaching Collection Slides. 35mm slides from the William Kelly Simpson teaching collection. Count of 99 black and white / color slides. New Kingdom, Thebes, 18th Dynasty. Slides featuring Khaemhat, Talatat, Rekhmire, and Ramose., 041091
  - Teaching Collection Slides. 35mm slides from the William Kelly Simpson teaching collection. Count of 84 black and white / color slides. New Kingdom, Thebes, Dynasty 18-20. Slides featuring Menna, Tjanuni, Userehet, Kherouef, the Ramesseum, and miscellaneous slides., 041092
  - Teaching Collection Slides. 35mm slides from the William Kelly Simpson teaching collection. Count of 74 black and white / color slides. New Kingdom, Thebes, mostly architectural features and wall paintings. Glass slides bound with red tape are fragile, handle with care., 041093
  - Teaching Collection Slides. 35mm slides from the William Kelly Simpson teaching collection. Count of 91 various black and white / color slides; various images of architecture, drawings, sculpture, and rock engravings. New Kingdom, mostly 19th dynasty. 19 from Abu Simbel; 21 from Abydos; 16 of Ramses II; 24 of Seti I; 11 miscellaneous 19th and 20th Dynasty slides., 041099
  - Teaching Collection Slides. 35mm slides from the William Kelly Simpson teaching collection. Count of 105 black and white / color slides. 70 slides of 18th-20th dynasty Karnak. 35 slides from the Third Intermediate Period, Dynasties 21-25; slides featuring reliefs, statuary, and vessels., 041100
  - Teaching Collection Slides. 35mm slides from the William Kelly Simpson teaching collection. Count of 82 black and white / color slides. 32 Late Dynastic slides (Dynasties 26, 27, 30); 36 Ptolemaic/Roman Period slides; 21 Miscellaneous slides. Slides feature statuary and architecture., 041101
  - Teaching Collection Slides. 35mm slides from the William Kelly Simpson teaching collection. Count of 102 black and white / color slides, miscellaneous modern diagrams, drawings, architectural features, and objects., 041102
  - Teaching Collection Slides. 35mm slides from the William Kelly Simpson teaching collection. Count of 119 black and white / color slides; various unlabeled miscellaneous sculpture, reliefs, landscapes, and drawings. 48 empty labeled cardboard slide frames., 041103
  - Teaching Collection Slides. 35mm slides from the William Kelly Simpson teaching collection. Count of 92 black and white / color slides. 18 possibly from the 1960's Pennsylvania-Yale Expedition; 14 personal photos of a mansion; 16 travel slides from Aswan, Luxor and Cairo; 23 labeled "Robert E. Murowchick 1977"; 16 from a 1970s expedition; 5 miscellaneous., 041104
  - Toshka East. Oversized Field Photos from Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 037956
  - Toshka East. Field Photos from Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 038195
  - Toshka West. Field Photos from Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 035193
  - Toshka West. Oversized Field Photos from Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 037957
  - Arminna West. Slides from Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 040126
  - Arminna East. Slides from Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 040127
  - Toshka West. Slides from Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 040128
  - Toshka East. Slides from Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 040129
  - Abydos. Field Photos from Penn-Yale Expedition to Egypt., 041126
  - Abydos. Oversize Field Photos from Penn-Yale Expedition to Egypt., 041129
  - Miscellaneous Mid-Size Publication Photos and Negatives, from Arminna West, Arminna East, Toshka East., 041819
  - Photographs of Wooden Objects with Coptic Inscriptions; found with materials from Abydos and the Penn -Yale Expedition to Egypt., 041839
  - Photographs of thin sections, likely from items excavated during Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 041849
  - Miscellaneous 35mm Negatives., 041860
  - Abydos. 120mm Negatives., 041872
  - 35mm slides from the Penn-Yale Expedition to Egypt, featuring Abydos, Cairo, Giza and Saqqara., 041883
- Field Notes, Series II
  General overviews.
  - Field Work Expenses, 1959-1960., 037098
  - Equipment, Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 037096
  - Personnel Applications Submitted to Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 037114
  - Personnel Accepted for Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 037115
  - Insurance for Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 037107
  - Other Field Work, Sudanese Nubia., 037113
  - Grant Applications and Related Materials for Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 037106
  - Expedition Reports, Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 037097
  - Field Work Expenses, 1961., 037099
  - Other Field Work, Yale University Prehistoric Expedition to Nubia (YUPEN)., 037111
  - Photo Registers, 1961., 037116
  - General Notes, Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 037105
  - Drawings from Arminna East and Toshka West, 1962., 037095
  - Field Work Expenses, 1962., 037100
  - Photo Registers, 1962., 037117
  - Field Work Expenses, 1963., 037101
  - Photo Registers, 1963., 037118
  - Field Work Expenses, 1964., 037102
  - Other Field Work, Dashur, Planning for Concession., 037110
  - Field Work Expenses, 1965., 037103
  - Field Work Expenses, 1966-1980, and n.d., 037104
  - Other Field Work, Abydos, Penn-Yale Expedition to Egypt., 037109
  - Other Field Work, Giza, Penn-Yale Expedition to Egypt., 037112
  - Journals/Ledgers from Field Work, Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia, Egypt., 036026
  - Object Records for Multiple Sites, Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 037108
  - Peabody Accession Notes for Objects from Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 037119
  - Working Copies of Simpson's Field Notebooks, 1961-1963, Pennsylvania- Yale Expedition to Nubia. Assembled by Randa Baligh, 1997., 042214
- Correspondence, Series III
  - 1959, William K Simpson Correspondence Regarding Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 037188
  - William K Simpson Correspondence with Bollingen Foundation Regarding Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia, 1959-1963., 037211
  - 1960, William K Simpson Correspondence Regarding Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 037189
  - 1960, William K Simpson Other Correspondence., 037190
  - William K Simpson Correspondence with State Department and UNESCO Regarding Preservation of Nubian Monuments and Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 037213
  - William K Simpson Correspondence Regarding Tutankhamun Exhibit of 1960's; Also Contractual Information, List of Objects and Related News Articles., 037210
  - 1961, William K Simpson Correspondence Regarding Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 037191
  - 1961, William K Simpson Other Correspondence., 037192
  - William K Simpson Correspondence with Paul Mellon Regarding Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia, 1961-1962., 037212
  - William K Simpson Correspondence Regarding Temple of Dendur Acquisition., 037209
  - William K Simpson Other Publication-Related Correspondence., 037215
  - 1962, William K Simpson Correspondence Regarding Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 037193
  - 1962, William K Simpson Other Correspondence., 037194
  - William K Simpson Correspondence Regarding Publication and Sale of Penn-Yale Expedition Publications, Volume 2, Late Nubian Settlement at Arminna West, Bruce Trigger., 037205
  - 1963, William K Simpson Correspondence Regarding Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 037195
  - 1963, William K Simpson Correspondence Regarding Trigger Article "A Meroitic Tomb Inscription from Toshka West"., 037196
  - 1963, William K Simpson Other Correspondence., 037197
  - William K Simpson Correspondence Regarding Publication and Sale of Penn-Yale Expedition Publications, Volume 1, Hekanefer and the Dynastic Material from Toshka and Arminna, William K Simpson., 037204
  - 1964, William K Simpson Correspondence Regarding Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 037198
  - 1964, William K Simpson Other Correspondence., 037199
  - William K Simpson Correspondence Regarding Publication and Sale of Penn-Yale Expedition Publications, Not Specific to Single Volume., 037203
  - William K Simpson Correspondence Regarding Publication and Sale of Penn-Yale Expedition Publications, Volume 3, Classic Christian Townsite at Arminna West, Kent Weeks., 037206
  - William K Simpson Correspondence Regarding Publication and Sale of Penn-Yale Expedition Publications, Volume 4, Meroitic Funerary Inscriptions from Arminna West, Bruce Trigger., 037207
  - William K Simpson Correspondence Regarding Objects from Penn-Yale Expedition and Peabody Museum., 037202
  - 1969-1970's, William K Simpson Correspondence Regarding Penn-Yale Expedition to Egypt., 037200
  - William K Simpson Correspondence Regarding Publication and Sale of Penn-Yale Expedition Publications, Volume 5, The Terrace of the Great God at Abydos, William K Simpson., 037208
  - William K Simpson Other Correspondence with Bruce Trigger., 037214
  - Unknown Date, William K Simpson, Correspondence Regarding Penn-Yale Expedition to Nubia., 037201
- Maps, Series IV
  - Arminna West. Mid-Sized Maps., 041813
  - Nubian Chronological Sequence., 037126
  - Arminna West Maps., 037127
  - General Maps for Yale-Penn Expedition to Nubia., 037128
  - Toshka West Maps., 037129
  - Miscellaneous Mid-Sized Maps., 041774
- Field Notes, Arminna East, Series V
  Field notes, find cards, and smaller illustrations stored in one box (along with Arminna West field notes, box 1 of 3). Oversize illustrations and images stored separately.
  - Arminna East. Rock Inscriptions, Arminna East. Amongst materials are copies of photos that are scanned and archived., 037143
  - Arminna East. Rock Tombs Excavation Notes, Drawings and Find Cards, Arminna East., 037144
  - Arminna East. Wine Press/Gold Washing Station and Other Cut-in-Rock Pits (Meroitic-Roman). Excavation Notes. Amongst materials are copies of photos that are already scanned and archived., 037145
  - Arminna East. Mid-size Flat Illustrations and Images., 041795
- Field Notes, Arminna West., Series VI
  Field notes, excavation and find cards, pottery forms, and smaller illustrations stored in three boxes (box 1 of 3 also houses Arminna East field notes). Oversize illustrations stored separately.
  - Arminna West. Cemetery A (AWA) Excavation Note and Find Cards., 037146
  - Arminna West. Cemetery A (AWA) Pottery Classification Forms., 037147
  - Arminna West. Cemetery B (AWB) Excavation Notes., 037148
  - Arminna West. Cemetery B (AWB) Object Drawings (Not Pottery)., 037149
  - Arminna West. Cemetery B (AWB) Pottery Classification Forms., 037150
  - Arminna West. Cemetery B (AWB) Pottery Discarded., 037151
  - Arminna West. Cemetery B (AWB) Pottery Drawings, Copies with Notes., 037152
  - Arminna West. Cemetery B (AWB) Pottery Drawings, Originals., 037153
  - Arminna West. Cemetery B (AWB) Pottery Notes., 037154
  - Arminna West. Cemetery B (AWB) Tomb 23 Lintel/Cornice. Amongst materials are copies of photos that are scanned and archived., 037155
  - Arminna West. Cemetery B (AWB) Tomb Sheets. These are copies of Tomb Sheets; originals have not been located., 037156
  - Arminna West. Cemetery C (AWC) Excavation Notes and Find Cards., 037157
  - Arminna West. Cemetery C (AWC) Pottery Classification Forms., 037158
  - Arminna West. Cemetery D (AWD) Pottery Classification Forms., 037159
  - Arminna West. Cemetery F (AWF) Excavation Notes and Tomb Sheets., 037160
  - Arminna West. Classic Christian Townsite Excavation Notes and Find Cards. The"Classic Christian Townsite" was originally identified as a Monastery. References in Field Notes to "Monastery" are referring to this site. Amongst materials are copies of photos that are scanned and archived., 037161
  - Arminna West. Classic Christian Townsite Object and Pottery Drawings. The"Classic Christian Townsite" was originally identified as a Monastery. References in Field Notes to "Monastery" are referring to this site., 037162
  - Arminna West. Correspondence regarding Cloth Samples sent to Louisa Bellinger., 037163
  - Arminna West. General Excavation Notes (Not Specific to a Single Site) and Other Find Cards for Arminna West., 037164
  - Arminna West. Measurements of Classic Christian Townsite and House B., 037165
  - Arminna West. Site Profile Notes., 037166
  - Arminna West. House Area E (AWE) Excavation Notes and Find Cards., 037167
  - Arminna West. House Area E (AWE) Pottery Classification Forms and Drawings., 037168
  - Arminna West. House Area K (AWK) Excavation Notes and Find Cards., 037169
  - Arminna West. House Area K (AWK) Pottery Drawings., 037170
  - Arminna West. Late Nubian Settlement Charcoal Samples., 037171
  - Arminna West. Late Nubian Settlement, Church and Adjacent Area, Coptic Stela Inscription., 037172
  - Arminna West. Late Nubian Settlement, Church and Adjacent Area, Greek Funerary Stela Inscription., 037173
  - Arminna West. Late Nubian Settlement, Church and Adjacent Areas, Object and Pottery Drawings., 037174
  - Arminna West. Late Nubian Settlement, Church and Adjacent Areas, Site Drawings and Notes., 037175
  - Arminna West. Late Nubian Settlement, House Area, Object and Pottery Drawings., 037176
  - Arminna West. Late Nubian Settlement, House Area, Site Drawings and Notes., 037177
  - Arminna West. Late Nubian Settlement, House X Object and Pottery Drawings., 037178
  - Arminna West. Late Nubian Settlement, House X Site Drawings and Notes., 037179
  - Arminna West. Late Nubian Settlement Object Log and Find Cards., 037180
  - Arminna West. Late Nubian Settlement, Western Building, Object and Pottery Drawings., 037181
  - Arminna West. Late Nubian Settlement, Western Building, Site Drawings and Notes., 037182
  - Arminna West. Meroitic Inscriptions. Amongst materials are copies of photos that are scanned and archived., 037183
  - Arminna West. Classic Christian Townsite Pottery Classification Forms. These forms are stored in two boxes due to volume.The "Classic Christian Townsite" was originally identified as a Monastery. References in Field Notes to "Monastery" are referring to this site. Box 1 contains folders 1-7: (1) No Room Number; (2) Room 001, Level 5 to Room 002/014, Level 2/3; (3) Room 003, Level 1 to Room 004/005, Level 2; (4) Room 005, Level 1 to Room 011, Level 2; (5) Room 012 "Oven" to Room 012b, Level 3; (6) Room 012c "Oven" to Room 012e, Level 4; (7) Room 012f, Level 2 to Room 013, Level 2. Box 2 contains folders 8-14: (8) Room 031 to Room 037; (9) Room 060, Level 1 to Room 068, Level 2; (10) Room 101 Level 1 to Room 105 "Fill to Floor"; (11) Room 106, Level 1 to Room 106 "Fill"; (12) Room 107, Level 1 to Room 110c, Level 1; (13) Room 111, Level 1 to Room 111c+d, Level 1; (14) Room 201, Level 1 to Room 203, Level 2, and miscellaneous papers., 037184
  - Arminna West. Cemetery B (AWB) Find Cards., 039180
  - Arminna West. Mid-size Flat Illustrations and Drawings., 041794
- Field Notes, Toshka East., Series VII
  Field notes, excavation and find cards, and smaller illustrations stored in one box. Oversize illustrations stored separately.
  - Toshka East, Crevice. Drawings. Photocopies of hieroglyphic graffiti with pencilled annotations; sheets fit together to make one image. Toshka East, crevice. Each sheet 26.8 cm L x 24.2 cm W. Graffiti description, sheet #1): Hekanefer No. 3, from west wall, southern half. Sheet #2) Hekanefer No. 1, from tomb site between Tombs I and II; Hekanefer No. 4, from crevice south wall; right-side portion of Hekanefer No. 3, from west wall southern half. Sheet #3) graffito of Re-Hotep, etc., from crevice west wall northern half. Publication: Simpson, "Hekanefer", Fig. 20, p.25., 041160
  - Toshka East. Cemetery A Excavation Notes., 037066
  - Toshka East. Cemetery B Excavation Notes., 037067
  - Toshka East. Gebel Agg Excavation Notes, Site Drawings and Field Cards., 037068
  - Toshka East. Gebel Agg Rock Inscriptions and Graffiti., 037069
  - Toshka East. Other Rock Inscriptions and Graffiti., 037070
  - Toshka East. Rock Tomb Drawings, Plans and Field Cards., 037071
  - Toshka East. Rock Tomb Inscriptions, Shawabti Texts (including ANT.222265)., 037072
  - Toshka East. Rock Tomb Inscriptions, Tomb I (Hekanefer)., 037073
  - Toshka East. Rock Tomb Pottery Drawings., 037074
  - Toshka East. Mid-size Flat Illustrations., 041792
- Field Notes, Toshka West., Series VIII
  Field notes, pottery log, find cards, and smaller illustrations stored in two boxes. Oversize illustrations stored separately.
  - Toshka West. Cemetery A (TWA) Drawings of Typical Tomb Types., 037075
  - Toshka West. Cemetery A (TWA) Excavation Notes., 037076
  - Toshka West. Cemetery A (TWA) Object Drawings., 037077
  - Toshka West. Cemetery A (TWA) Object Logs and Summaries., 037078
  - Toshka West. Cemetery A (TWA) Pottery Drawings., 037079
  - Toshka West. Cemetery A (TWA) Pottery Log., 037080
  - Toshka West. Cemetery A (TWA) Tomb Records/Find Cards. Stored in four folders for convenience. Sorted by Tomb Number within folders. Folder 1 contains Tombs 1 to 50. Folder 2 contains Tombs 51 to 100. Folder 3 contains Tombs 101-198. Folder 4 contains Appendices which summarize objects found across tombs, categorized by material., 037081
  - Toshka West. Cemetery A (TWA) Tomb Sheets. Stored in two folders for convenience. Sorted by Tomb Number within folders. Folder 1 contains Tombs 1 to 75. Folder 2 contains Tombs 76-198 and Tombs S1-S2., 037082
  - Toshka West. Cemetery A (TWA) Inscriptions., 037083
  - Toshka West. Cemetery B (TWB) Insciption on Jar Sealing (TWB 2.4)., 037084
  - Toshka West. Cemetery B (TWB) Object Log and Find Cards., 037085
  - Toshka West. Cemetery B (TWB) Tomb Sheets., 037086
  - Toshka West. Cemetery C (TWC) Object Log and Find Cards., 037087
  - Toshka West. Cemetery C (TWC) Tomb Sheets., 037088
  - Toshka West. Cemetery D (TWD) Excavation Notes and Find Cards., 037089
  - Toshka West. Cemetery D (TWD) Tomb Sheets., 037090
  - Toshka West. Dynastic Inscriptions., 037091
  - Toshka West. Bead and Object Drawings by Hubert Queloz, 1962., 037092
  - Toshka West. Pottery Drawings (Cemeteries A-D) by Hubert Queloz, 1962., 037093
  - Toshka West. Field notes and find cards for House A., 037094
  - Toshka West. Find Cards for Objects Obtained from Local Village (TWV)., 039175
  - Toshka West. Two pages of documentation related to Meroitic glass flask ANT.262463, from Cemetery A, Toshka West. Found with field photo ANTAR.034763 and removed for proper storage. Documentation includes an object drawing and a page from an auction catalog (?) featuring a flask similar to ANT.262463., 040683
  - Toshka West. Mid-size Flat Illustrations., 041793